Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Int'l. Ship Suppliers Association, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 8: International Salt Company: Public Law 91-508 Disclosure Notice, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 9: International Salt Company: Absentee Report, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 10: The Akzo America Merit Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 11: Accident Insurance Program for salaried employees of Akzo America Inc., Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 12: Akzo America Retirement Plan for salaried employees of International Salt Company, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 13: Personnel Profile, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 14: Determination of Pay Allowance for Military Training, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 15: Employees Matching Gifts Plan: A Plan for Matching Gifts Made by Employees to Educational Institutions, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 16: Request Form for Salaried Employees, Exempt and Non-Exempt, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 17: Individual Business Ethics, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 18: Day of Rest for Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 19: Direct Deposit Approval Form, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 20: Application for Employment: Exempt Position, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 21: Welcome to the Thirty-First Annual Old Timers' Banquet of the Watkins Glen Refinery International Salt Company, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    September 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: International Salt Company: In Recognition of Your Service, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 23: A Salty Story, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 24: International Salt Company: Personnel Change Authorization, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 25: Proof of Employee's Death, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 26: Tuition Refund Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 27: International Salt Company Merit Salary Review: Non-Exempt Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 28: International Salt Company Merit Salaary Review: Exempt Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 29: Beneficiary Designation, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 30: Corporate Industrial Relations Manual, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    Effective: April 13, 1973; Revised: July 1, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Corporate Industrial Relations Manual, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    Effective: December 31, 1961; Revised: December 31, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Corporate Industrial Relations Manual, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    Effective: April 14, 1961; Revised: July 1, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Corporate Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    Effective: April 19, 1965; Revised: October 1, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Corporate Industrial Relations Manual, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    Effective: October 4, 1962; Revised: August 1, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Industrial Relations Division Chart, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Item 36: The Shaker Newsletter Number 8, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    July 16, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: The Insider, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    May 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Corporate Industrial Relations Manual, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    Effective: April 14, 1961; Revision: October 1, 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Letter Concerning Group Benefits Enrollment from Patricia A. Lewis, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
    By Patricia A. Lewis. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Your Company Your Job Your Benefits: A Guide for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Int'l. Society of certified Employee Benefit Specialists, Publication (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The History of ISSA, Publication (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Interstate Conference of Employment Security Agencies, Publication (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Expert Opinion: Taking Stock of Pension Poilcy, Retirement Goals, Publication (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Census of Certified Employee Benefit Specialists, Publication (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: Census of Certified Employee Benefit Specialists, Publication (Box 17, Folder 37)
    June 1990. Item is in English.
- Ithaco, Publication (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Interstate Conference of Employment Security Agencies Information Folder, Publication (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Iowa Old Age Assistance Commission, Publication (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Ithaco Annual Report 1988, Publication (Box 17, Folder 39)
- James River Corporation, Publication (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Revision of Rating System in Use by the Iowa Old Age Assistance Commission, Publication (Box 17, Folder 40)
    By Lloyd A. Knowler and Donald A. Trauger. January 1937. Item is in English.
- Japan Productivity Center, Publication (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: James River Corporation: Product and Service Performance, Publication (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: James River Corporation: Strategy Statement, Publication (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Jewish Labor Committee, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Five Who Led, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Labor Rights in the Jewish Tradition, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    By Michael S. Perry. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Jewish Labor Committee and the American Jewish Community, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Jewish Labor Committee Support for Labor Struggles, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Jewish Labor Committee News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Jewish Labor Committee: Why Labor Supports Israel, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Jewish Labor Committee Review, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    December 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Program Highlights: JLC Support for Issues of Concern to the Jewish Community, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: 1992 Survey: Critique of Trade Union Rights in Countries Affiliated with the League of Arab States, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    By Michael S. Perry. June 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Jewish Labor Committee Review, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Spring 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: 1995 Survey: Critique of Trade Union Rights in Countries Affiliated with the League of Arab States, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    By Philip Stern and Arieh Lebowitz. Item is in English.
- Jewish Labor Committee, Atran Center and Anti-Defamation League of B'mai B'rith, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Pioneers of Labor, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Jobs with Peace Campaign - Books not bombs! Putting our money where our minds are, April 1984, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Books not Bombs! Putting our money where our minds are., Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    First Printing: April 1984. Item is in English.
- John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance-Co., Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: News Line Vol. 3, No. 12, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    June 11, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Business Line Vol. 4, No. 2, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    January 28, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: About the John Hancock, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Idea Center, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Your Security Program, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Performance Management Program, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Flyer 1, For New Members: Flex Plan '88: Reflecting Changing Needs, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Flyer 2, For New Members: Flex Plan '88: Reflecting Changing Needs, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Flyer 3, For New Members: Flex Plan '88: Reflecting Changing Needs, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Flyer 4, For New Members: Flex Plan '88: Reflecting Changing Needs, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Flyer 5, For New Members: Flex Plan '88: Reflecting Changing Needs, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Flyer 6, For New Members: Flex Plan '88: Reflecting Changing Needs, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Flex Plan '88: Reflecting Changing Needs, Your Enrollment Workbook for District Managers, Staff Managers and Subsidiary Employees, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: A Challenge for the 1990's Work Force Diversity at John Hancock, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: The John Hancock Complex, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: John Hancock Employee Information Catalog, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: John Hancock 1993 Annual Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
- John L. Lewis Commission, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: John L. Lewis Comission, Inc. Newsletter, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
    December 1990. Item is in English.
- Johns-Manville Corporation - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Johns-Manville Application, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Survivor Income, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: You and J-M Building Security for your Tomorrows, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Manville: Manville Worldwide Directory of Products and Operations, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Manville, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: 1985 Corporate Profile, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: General Information for New Employees, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: WPAR Record: Work Plan and Performance Description, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Manville Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Johns Manville Corporation - "Employee Handbook", 1981; Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Your U.S. Salaried Employees Thrift Plan, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Manville: U.S. Salaried Employees Dental Plan, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    January 1, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: U.S. Administrators, Inc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Investment Plans, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Johnson and Johnson - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Johnson & Johnson, People Helping People, and its worldwide family of companies, Publication (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: 1990 Congressional and Regulatory Issues, Publication (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Johnson & Johnson Family of Companies, Publication (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Johnson & Johnson 1988 Annual Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: A Brief History of Johnson & Johnson, Publication (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Johnson & Johnson Information Folder, Publication (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Johnson & Johnson Baby Products Company, Publication (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Employee Assistance Program: Supervisory Training Manual, Publication (Box 18, Folder 9)
- S.C. Johnson & Son, Inc. - handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Assessment Center at Johnson's Wax, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
    By M. G. Shankster and D. J. Cordea. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Just Ask, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Johnson Wax: Weekly, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
    November 20, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Johnson Wax: Manager Performance Appraisal Program, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Health Care Claims Instructions: Programs for you., Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Benefit Request Form Medical Care Benefits, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Benefit Request Form Vision Care Benefits, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Benefit Request Form Dental Care Benefits, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Benefit Expense Account, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: This Company of Ours, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Johnson Wax: Benefits, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Johnson Wax: Benefits, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Johnson Wax: Child Care Center, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Johnson Wax Child Care Center, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Johson Wax: This We Believe, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Johson Wax: This We Believe, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Your Comments on Food Services, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Just Ask, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Employee Performance Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Employee Data Questionnaire for executives, supervisors, specialized, scientists and engineers, & sales, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Johnson Wax: Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Johnson Wax: Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Quality of Life! Racine, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Quality of Life! Racine, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Johnson Wax Magazine: Johnson's Expedition to the Skies, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Winter 1984/84. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Flexible Hours Policy Updated, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
    May 10, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Johnson Wax Weekly, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
    August 8, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Johnson Wax Weekly, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
    July 18, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Flexible Hours Policy Updated, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: Employee Data Questionnaire for executives, supervisors, specialized, scientists and engineers, & sales( All EXEMPT Personnel), Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 31: Equal Opportunity: ConcernsInvolvementResults, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Joint Labor Legislative Board, Publication (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Missouri Legislative Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The New Strength in Steel., Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: 1. Program Introduction, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: 2. Workbook, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: 3. Benefit Bank, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: 4. Health Care, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: 5. Disability Income, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: 6. Life & Accident Insurance, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: 7. Capital Accumulation Plan, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: 8. Retirement Income, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: 9. Vacations & Holidays, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: 10. General Information, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Forms, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation We Know That Good People Will Make Tomorrow Happen, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Program of Insurane Benefits for Hourly Paid Employees of Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Amended January 1, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Equal Employment Opportunity Policy, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: Pension Agreement between Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America with Summary Plan Description, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Effective July 31, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Confidential Management Review of Performance Checklist: Nonexempt, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: Confidential Management Review of Performance Summary: Nonexempt, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 19: Confidential Management Review of Performance Summary, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: Jones & Laughlin Letter to All Employees, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
    August 17, 1983. Item is in English.
- K Mart Corp. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: K Mart Corporation: Opportunities Unlimited, Publication (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: K Mart Corporation 1987 Annual Report: Making a Good Idea Better., Publication (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: K Mart: Opportunities Unlimited, Publication (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: K Mart Information Kit, Publication (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corp. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Advertisement, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical Corporation, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Kaiser Aluminum: The Corporation at a Glance, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
    May 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Form 10-K Securities and Exchange Commission, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Kaiser Aluminum Corporation: 2nd Quarter Report 1994, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Kaiser Aluminum Corporation Annual Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Kaiser Aluminum Corporation: 1st Quarter Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Kane Company, Publication (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A Memorandum of Understanding by and between The Chairman of the Kane County Board, and the Chairman of the Labor Management Committee of the Kane County Board, and the Sheriff of Kane County, Publication (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Kansas City Board of Juvenile Welfare, Publication (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Industrial Accidents in Missouri, Publication (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Kelly Communications, Publication (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Medical Benefits: The Medical-Economic Digest, Publication (Box 18, Folder 17)
    September 30, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Medical Benefits: The Medical-Economic Digest, Publication (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Kennecott - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Kennecott, Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Kennecott: Its Men and Minerals, Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Personal Development History, Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Personal Development Plan, Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Equal Employment Practices: A Special Report, South Africa, Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Kohler Company - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Kohler, Publication (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Employee Handbook: Administrative Non-Exempt, Publication (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Safety and the Kohler Co., Publication (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Kohler, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    May 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    February 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    April 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    May 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    June 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    March 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    June 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    September 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    August 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    October 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: People: Published monthly for Kohler Co. employees and their families, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)